You know, it's really important to address that like me making this in this time was my own
decision to do because I wanted to make something. But it's somehow serendipitously speaks to the
fact that so many of us at this point are only going to get to make something if we make it by
ourselves or if we make it with an indie. That is what we're striking about is that, you know,
these networks, they are not fair in terms of how they're sharing profits around intellectual
property. They're also not consistent in their hiring practices. And also, I mean, we have the
AI of it all where they're like, well, even if you are some unique talent, we can just take that
print it and copy paste it. And now we got that unique talent in our files. So your safety as like
an intellectual creative is only preserved if you're making stuff by yourself as well. I mean,
and even that's a little bit sketchy wet because the internet is a breeding ground for let me hold
that real quick.